🗷 sgchi@purdue.edu | 🎢 engineering.purdue.edu/people/seunggeun.chi.1 | 🖸 sgchi | 🛅 seunggeun-chi-963050153 | 🎓 Seunggeun Chi

Research Interests

My research interests lie in **Machine Learning** and its applications to real-world problems. **Representation Learning** in **Computer Vision** problems is my primary study. My research also spans over **Combinatorial Optimization** problems which aim to extract rules by applying **Reinforcement Learning**.

Education

Purdue University West Lafayette, U.S.

Ph.D. Student in Electrical and Computer Engineering

Aug. 2021 - current

• C-Design Lab, Advisor: Karthik Ramani

Seoul National University Seoul, S. Korea

M.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

Mar. 2019 - Aug. 2021

• Optimization Lab, Advisor : ByungRo Moon

Seoul National University

Seoul, S.Korea

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

Mar. 2013 - Feb. 2019

Computer Architecture Lab, Advisor: SangLyul Min

Publications & Patents

Conference Proceedings

- S. Chi*, H. Chi*, Q. Huang, K. Ramani. Skeleton-ODE: Learning Representation by Predicting the Future for Online Skeleton-based Action Recognition. IEEE Transactions on Pattern Analysis and Machine Intelligence (T-PAMI), submitted
- [C3] S. Chi*, H. Chi*, S. Chan, K. Ramani. Pose Relation Transformer: Refine Occlusions for Human Pose Estimation. *IEEE International Conference on Robotics and Automation (ICRA)*, 2023
- [C2] H. Chi, M. H. Ha, S. Chi, S. Lee, Q. Huang, K. Ramani. InfoGCN: Representation Learning for Human Skeleton-based Action Recognition. IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2022
- [C1] M. H. Ha, S. Chi, S. Lee, Y. Cha, B. R. Moon. Evolution-based Meta Reinforcement Learning for Portfolio Optimization. In proceedings of the 23rd *The Genetic and Evolutionary Computation Conference (GECCO), 2021*

Patent

 K.Ramani, H.Chi, S.Chi. Pose Relation Transformer And Refining Occlusions For Human Pose Estimation. U.S. Patent Application (MMB 1743-0299P)

Other Tools and Skills

Skills

Research and Development Stacks

Major LanguagesPython, C/C++, java, VerilogOther LangaugesShell Scripts(bszh, zsh), Matlab, RMachine LearningPyTorch, TensorFlowOperating SystemsmacOS, Linux Debian/Ubuntu, WindowsComputer VisionOpenCV, OpenGLText Editors & IDEVim, VSCode, Eclipse

 Web Languages
 Nginx, HTML5, PHP, JavaScript, CSS
 Software
 SolidWorks, Catia, AutoCAD

Database MySQL, SQLite VCS Git

Research & Project

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Action Diffusion Model: Composing action from text-based input with Diffusion Model

C-Design Lab, Purdue Univ. Mar. 2023 -

• Aligned motion representation and text representation in the latent space.

Developed latent diffusion model for effective diffusion process.

• Established novel action composition algorithm.

Skeleton-based action sequence generation with salient atomic actions

C-Design Lab, Purdue Univ.

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

- Encode latent action trajectory with Neural ODE.
- · Extract the salient action frames of actions, and define atomic actions with the salient action frames.
- Apply diffusion model to generate continuous action sequences with atomic actions.

SEUNGGEUN CHI · CURRICULUM VITAE

Designing spatial-navigation on chrome-extension

ArchiLab, Seoul National Univ.

RESEARCH ASSISTANT Sep. 2018 - Dec. 2018

- · formulated malfunctioning cases and defined user-friendly environment
- Developed user-friendly navigation UI
- https://github.com/WICG/spatial-navigation

Academic Activities

Reviewer

- The IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2023
- Conference on Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS), 2023

Education Outreach

- Gifted Education Research & Resource Institute (GER²I), 2022 Summer

Working Experience _____

SK Hynix Icheon, S.Korea

Intern Researcher Sep. 2017 - Dec. 2017

- · Designed an exclusive chip for testing 3D NAND flash architecture and verified the reliabilty of existing architectures
- Developed a module for predicting locality of data and tested it with real data

Korean National Police Agency

Dokdo, S.Korea

AUXILIARY POLICE

Dec. 2013 - Sep. 2015

Teaching Experience

Seoul National University

CS.4190.681A	Genetic Algorithm, 2019-spring, 2021-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.4190.407	Algorithm, 2019-fall, 2020-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.M1522.407	Data Structure , 2019-spring, 2020-spring, 2021-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.4190.308	Computer architecture, 2018-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.035.001	Digital Computer Concept and Practice, 2017-fall, 2018-fall	Teaching Assistant
PE.051.004	Volley ball, 2018-fall, 2019-spring, 2021-spring	Teaching Assistant

Honors & Awards

Competition of accelerating General-Purpose GPU sponsored by Intel

Manycore Programming Lab

1ST PLACI

2018

The National Scholarship for Science and Engineering

Korea Ministry of Science and ICT

FULL SCHOLARSHIP

Mar. 2018 - Aug. 2021

Invited Talk

Yonsei University Seoul, S.Korea

GUEST LECTURER: REPRESENTATION LEARNING FOR HUMAN ACTION RECOGNITION AND GENERATION

Apr. 2023

Purdue Interdisciplinary Graduate Programs

West Lafayette

PRESENTER: REPRESENTATION LEARNING FOR HUMAN SKELETON-BASED ACTION RECOGNITION

May. 2023